[
    {
        "question": "JavaScript is the programming language of HTML and the Web.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript is the programming language of HTML and the Web."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript is one of the 3 languages all web developers must learn, HTML to define the content of web pages, CSS to specify the layout of web pages, and JavaScript to program the behaviour of web pages.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "is one of the 3 languages all web developers must learn, HTML to define the content of web pages, CSS to specify the layout of web pages, and JavaScript to program the behaviour of web pages."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaSCript can only be used with Web pages.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "Web pages are not the only place where JavaScript is used. Many desktop and server programs use JavaScript. Node.js is the best known."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript and Java are identical languages, both in concept and design.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "JavaScript and Java are completely different languages, both in concept and design."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript was invented by Brendan Eich in 1995, and became an ECMA standard in 1997.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript was invented by Brendan Eich in 1995, and became an ECMA standard in 1997."
    },
    {
        "question": " ECMA-262 is the official name of the standard. ECMAScript is the official name of the language.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": " ECMA-262 is the official name of the standard. ECMAScript is the official name of the language."
    },
    {
        "question": "Javascript can be enbedded in the HTML document. The code must be inserted between <javascript> and </javascript> tags.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "Javascript can be enbedded in the HTML document. The code must be inserted between <script> and </script> tags."
    },
    {
        "question": "This line of code \" document.writeline( \"<h1>Welcome to JavaScript Programming</h1>\" ); \" will display the phrase \"Welcome to JavaScript Programming\" as an h1 heading in the web page.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "This line of code \" document.writeline( \"<h1>Welcome to JavaScript Programming</h1>\" ); \" will display the phrase \"Welcome to JavaScript Programming\" as an h1 heading in the web page."
    },
    {
        "question": "You can only place one script in an HTML document.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "You can place any number of scripts in an HTML document."
    },
    {
        "question": "Scripts can be placed in the <body>, or in the <head> section of an HTML page, or in both.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Scripts can be placed in the <body>, or in the <head> section of an HTML page, or in both."
    },
    {
        "question": "Placing scripts at the bottom of the <body> element improves the display speed, because script compilation slows down the display.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Placing scripts at the bottom of the <body> element improves the display speed, because script compilation slows down the display."
    },
    {
        "question": "Scripts can also be placed in external files.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Scripts can also be placed in external files."
    },
    {
        "question": "To use an external script, put the name of the script file in the href attribute of a <script> tag:",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "To use an external script, put the name of the script file in the src (source) attribute of a <script> tag:"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can place an external script reference only in the <head>.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "You can place an external script reference in <head> or <body> as you like."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript files have the file extension .js .",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript files have the file extension .js ."
    },
    {
        "question": "External scripts are placed inside <script> tags.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "External scripts cannot contain <script> tags."
    },
    {
        "question": "Placing scripts in external files has the following advantages, It separates HTML and code, It makes HTML and JavaScript easier to read and maintain, and Cached JavaScript files can speed up page loads.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Placing scripts in external files has the following advantages, It separates HTML and code, It makes HTML and JavaScript easier to read and maintain, and Cached JavaScript files can speed up page loads."
    },
    {
        "question": "In HTML, JavaScript programs are executed by the web browser.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In HTML, JavaScript programs are executed by the web browser."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript statements are composed of Values, and Expressions.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "JavaScript statements are composed of Values, Operators, Expressions, Keywords, and Comments."
    },
    {
        "question": "When separated by semicolons, multiple statements on one line are allowed.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "When separated by semicolons, multiple statements on one line are allowed."
    },
    {
        "question": "If a JavaScript statement does not fit on one line, the best place to break it is after an operator as \"=, +, ...\".",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "If a JavaScript statement does not fit on one line, the best place to break it is after an operator as \"=, +, ...\"."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript statements can be grouped together in code blocks, inside square brackets [...].",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript statements can be grouped together in code blocks, inside curly brackets {...}."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript keywords are reserved words. Reserved words cannot be used as names for variables.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript keywords are reserved words. Reserved words cannot be used as names for variables."
    },
    {
        "question": "This line of code is legal in JavaScript: a = 5; b = 6; c = a + b;",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "This line of code is legal in JavaScript: a = 5; b = 6; c = a + b;"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can use conditional statements in your code to perform different actions for different decisions.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "You can use conditional statements in your code to perform different actions for different decisions."
    },
    {
        "question": "Use else to specify a block of code to be executed, if the same condition is false.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Use else to specify a block of code to be executed, if the same condition is false."
    },
    {
        "question": "Use if to specify a block of code to be executed, if a specified condition is true.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Use if to specify a block of code to be executed, if a specified condition is true."
    },
    {
        "question": "Use switch to specify many alternative blocks of code to be executed.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Use switch to specify many alternative blocks of code to be executed."
    },
    {
        "question": "A for loop repeats until a specified condition evaluates to true.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "A for loop repeats until a specified condition evaluates to false."
    },
    {
        "question": "In a for loop, If the value of condition is true, the loop statements execute. If the value of condition is false, the for loop terminates. If the condition expression is omitted entirely, the condition is assumed to be true.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In for loop, If the value of condition is true, the loop statements execute. If the value of condition is false, the for loop terminates. If the condition expression is omitted entirely, the condition is assumed to be true."
    },
    {
        "question": "To execute multiple statements, use a block statement ({ ... }) to group those statements.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": " To execute multiple statements, use a block statement ({ ... }) to group those statements."
    },
    {
        "question": "In a for loop, If present, the update expression incrementExpression is executed.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In a for loop, If present, the update expression incrementExpression is executed."
    },
    {
        "question": "In a while loop, If the condition becomes false, statement within the loop stops executing and control passes to the statement following the loop.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In a while loop, If the condition becomes false, statement within the loop stops executing and control passes to the statement following the loop."
    },
    {
        "question": "If the condition in a loop never becomes false, the loop will never terminate.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "If the condition in a loop never becomes false, the loop will never terminate."
    },
    {
        "question": "The do/while loop is a variant of the while loop. This loop will execute the code block once, before checking if the condition is true, then it will repeat the loop as long as the condition is true.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "The do/while loop is a variant of the while loop. This loop will execute the code block once, before checking if the condition is true, then it will repeat the loop as long as the condition is true."
    },
    {
        "question": "The switch statement is used to perform different actions based on different conditions.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "The switch statement is used to perform different actions based on different conditions."
    },
    {
        "question": "In a switch statement, if there is a match, the associated block of code is executed.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In a switch statement, if there is a match, the associated block of code is executed."
    },
    {
        "question": "In a swicth statement, when JavaScript reaches a break keyword, it breaks out of the switch block. And then start over again until no match is found.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "When JavaScript reaches a break keyword, it breaks out of the switch block."
    },
    {
        "question": "It is necessary to break the last case in a switch block.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "It is not necessary to break the last case in a switch block."
    },
    {
        "question": "If you omit the break statement, the next case will be executed even if the evaluation does not match the case.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "If you omit the break statement, the next case will be executed even if the evaluation does not match the case."
    },
    {
        "question": "The default keyword specifies the code to run if there is no case match.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "The default keyword specifies the code to run if there is no case match."
    },
    {
        "question": "A string (or a text string) is a series of characters like \"Athabasca University\".",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "A string (or a text string) is a series of characters like \"Athabasca University\"."
    },
    {
        "question": "Strings are written with double quotes only.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "Strings are written with quotes. You can use single or double quotes."
    },
    {
        "question": "In JavaScript, there are 3 types of quotes: Double quotes, Single quotes, and Backticks.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In JavaScript, there are 3 types of quotes: Double quotes, Single quotes, and Backticks."
    },
    {
        "question": "Double and single quotes are simple quotes. There’s no difference between them in JavaScript.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Double and single quotes are simple quotes. There’s no difference between them in JavaScript."
    },
    {
        "question": "Backticks are “extended functionality” quotes. They allow us to embed variables and expressions into a string by wrapping them in ${…}.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Backticks are “extended functionality” quotes. They allow us to embed variables and expressions into a string by wrapping them in ${…}."
    },
    {
        "question": "JavaScript has only one type of numbers.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "JavaScript has only one type of numbers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Numbers can only be written with decimals.",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "Numbers can be written with, or without decimals."
    },
    {
        "question": "The number type represents both integer and floating point numbers.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "The number type represents both integer and floating point numbers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Infinity, -Infinity and NaN are special numeric values that belongs to the Number data type.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Infinity, -Infinity and NaN are special numeric values that belongs to the Number data type."
    },
    {
        "question": "Infinity represents the mathematical Infinity ∞. We can get it as a result of division by zero.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Infinity represents the mathematical Infinity ∞. We can get it as a result of division by zero."
    },
    {
        "question": "NaN represents a computational error. It is a result of an incorrect or an undefined mathematical operation.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "NaN represents a computational error. It is a result of an incorrect or an undefined mathematical operation."
    },
    {
        "question": "NaN is sticky. Any further operation on NaN returns NaN. So, if there’s a NaN somewhere in a mathematical expression, it propagates to the whole result.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "NaN is sticky. Any further operation on NaN returns NaN. So, if there’s a NaN somewhere in a mathematical expression, it propagates to the whole result."
    },
    {
        "question": "The boolean type has only two values: true and false.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "The boolean type has only two values: true and false."
    },
    {
        "question": "In JavaScript Everything With a \"Value\" is True, and Everything Without a \"Value\" is False.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In JavaScript Everything With a \"Value\" is True, and Everything Without a \"Value\" is False."
    },
    {
        "question": "Syntax of creating an Array is: var array_name = [item1, item2, ...]; or var array_name = new Array(item1, item2, ...);",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Syntax of creating an Array is: var array_name = [item1, item2, ...]; or var array_name = new Array(item1, item2, ...);"
    },
    {
        "question": "This expression returns false: Boolean(10 > 9)",
        "answer": "false",
        "correct": "This expression returns true: Boolean(10 > 9)"
    },
    {
        "question": "These are true values in JavaScript: 20, -1, 3.14, 1 + 2, \"false\", true.",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "In JavaScript Everything With a \"Value\" is True, and Everything Without a \"Value\" is False."
    },
    {
        "question": "These are false values in JavaScript: 0, -0, \"\", '', null, false, (10 / \"H\").",
        "answer": "true",
        "correct": "Syntax of creating an Array is: var array_name = [item1, item2, ...]; or var array_name = new Array(item1, item2, ...);"
    }
]